Hi everyone! I'm on Malta again for the Dark Malta Festival. It was so good last year that
I came back obviously but it's already the last day of my vacation tonight I'm
going to party on Malta hence the outfit but I needed an intro for the Dark Malta video so
you see all this messy room glory here with me what was new this year at Dark
Malta we had a pool party so I'm going to show you that and also I talked to
some bands and asked them what the festival is like for bands I hope you
enjoy it here we go I'm here with Eric 13 and you the official host of this
year's Dark Martyr I am indeed tell me what is the job of a host be here you
must smile three things and look good but you do have to talk right and I and
I introduced the best and I also that's the job you introduce the band also I
introduced the best arrived two hours before the first band I stayed two hours
after the last band. I never leave the festival. I never...
You live here now?
Yeah, I have a bedroom in the back, they have a guest suite, and I will do it again tonight,
and I will do it again tomorrow. So it's a little more work actually to be the host.
How do you like the festival so far? We're on day two.
Day two. I think it's been really special this year. I think day one, the bands were
happy, the fans were happy, everyone's free. And I was here last year, wonderful festival,
But I think this year is even better.
I saw you last year here.
You were playing.
What do you prefer, being here as a host or as a band member?
I would say I prefer to play.
But this is really fun.
This is really fun.
I enjoy hosting.
I enjoy talking to people, making a good party.
I'm naturally friendly and you know.
So what's your plan for next year?
You know, I got to ask Renee.
I guess I come back.
Maybe I'm the chef.
You know, maybe I'm sweeping up afterwards, I don't know.
Picking up people from the airport, I don't know.
Whatever he wants.
I'll see you in the pool now.
Yeah, I'm gonna go to the pool.
Hi, I'm here with Frozen Plasma.
You're playing tonight guys.
Are you already excited?
We are excited like hell, yeah.
We are very excited.
As always.
But even more here because it's a special place of course.
We are playing under palm trees and with sunshine and so at home we have like 10 degrees less.
So yeah, we're in a reggae mood.
Yeah, I'm so glad to be here.
Yeah, it's a shorter set tonight, like 45 minutes less than usually.
So it will be very powerful.
Full power set.
Okay, I'm looking forward to see that and I will evaluate later on.
So I'll tell you if it really was for power.
Okay, the power rate.
The power rate.
Power rate, oh.
Did you see a lot of Marta so far?
No, I arrived last night at 8pm and I'm leaving tomorrow at 2pm.
So I don't have time for a lot of sightseeing.
Why?
Because I'm an idiot.
You're causing misunderstanding.
I came for the show, I don't care for the tourism.
So for next year you have to come earlier and stay longer?
I gave myself a reason to come back, you know?
Yeah.
We have several bands.
The reason why we have several bands is to play festivals like this one.
Don't give away our secret.
Do you have something special planned for tonight for your outfits?
Oh, we have.
Yeah, I think we change our outfits in 45 minutes as often as we didn't before ever.
All the years now.
Right?
So like three different outfits in 45 minutes.
So is it holiday themed or what's the theme?
It's a...
Glamour?
Yeah.
It's a glamorous, 80s, sexy theme.
I mean, at least he's sexy, I'm not sexy.
I just follow his clothing advices.
Okay, then I'm looking forward to it and I'll see you guys tonight on stage.
Thanks for joining me.
But how did you come to your name, Selen Nox?
Well, it's a variation of my actual name.
Then I needed a surname, so I just chose something randomly, like Mox.
Okay.
Are you satisfied?
Because everybody is asking us, if you meet Selene, ask her about her name.
So now we know the secret.
Okay.
So we do not change.
We reveal secrets of the outfits and you reveal the secret of your name.
That's a fair deal.
If you have some special outfits for tonight, because no?
I will change for tonight.
I mean for him.
Oh, for you?
Sorry, I only got girls clothes with me.
That works sometimes too, you know?
alright
thanks
thank you
enjoy the show
the numbers
right
the voices
wrong
it's killing
time
I have no
choice
what will
happen to
me
tell me
which
loves
killing
the mercy
and that
man's
winning
over the
sea
he wants
to be
Okay, late night in the view, it's already dark, you're going to play in a few hours,
Empathy Test.
Is it your first time here?
Yeah, first time in Malta, first time in dark Malta obviously.
Yeah, it's been really, really great fun and we've been well looked after and we haven't
even performed yet.
I heard that there are a lot of bands who want to play there, so how does it work?
Do you have to like apply to play here?
Well, we were invited.
Oh, that's nice.
I don't know whether that happens for everyone, but yeah, I think we were requested and Rene
is super happy to have us here.
He said, finally, you're here.
So yeah, it's great to be here.
Did you see something from the aisle today? Did you go sightseeing?
Yeah, I mean it's always such a whirlwind and we arrived last night quite late and it was already dark when we arrived.
we came here uh watched a couple of bands uh and then went to the hotel to sleep and then today um
yeah i went for a swim in the sea oh yeah is the sea cold how cold is it i would say it's probably
the same temperature as the sea is in the summer you know like in england yeah yeah it was very
refreshing. It's very brave of you. Yeah I came well I have this thing where I if there's a body
of water I always end up in it somehow so I saw the sea and it looked amazing and I was like I
have to go in there and I thought I'd be in there two minutes and then have to run out but I was
swimming around for a while until my toes went numb. Do you plan something special for tonight's
or is it just... Not really, I mean it's a festival and we only have 45 minutes so we
cram as many of the hits into the 45 minutes as we can. You know it's funny, I heard it
today already, it's only 45 minutes so it sounds like it's a bad thing. It's too short
really. It's too short. Yeah, I mean for us, maybe for the audience that's fine. I'd love
to hear more from you than 45 minutes you know.
Two weeks ago we were in America, we flew 10 hours in each way for 45 minutes on stage.
So two hour flight for 45 minutes is much better I guess.
Okay so I hope you enjoy your time tonight.
Thank you very much.
Thanks for taking the time to chat with me.
And have fun.
Yeah you too.
Thanks.
Scared of losing touch, I really mean that much
Why pretend that you love him?
Don't call me out for blue
It's clear that I still do
You know he knows it too
Going home alone
The only love I've known
It's always been you
You know I love the other festivals,
Mariluna, Amphi, Wacken, Coachella, all cool,
but Dark Malta manages to be unique.
Next year, I'll be the new host of The Celine Knot Show.
This is Eric Durtine, signing off.